(crowd cheers)
♪ Can't see nothin' in front of me ♪
♪ Can't see nothin' comin' up behind ♪
♪ Make my way through this darkness ♪
♪ Can't feel nothin' but
this chain that binds me ♪
♪ Lost track of how far I've gone ♪
♪ How far I've gone,
how high I've climbed ♪
♪ On my back's a 60-pound stone ♪
♪ On my shoulder a half mile of line ♪
♪ Come on up for the rising ♪
♪ Come on up, lay your hands in mine ♪
♪ Come on up for the rising tonight ♪
♪ Left the house this monrnin' ♪
♪ Bells ringing filled the air ♪
♪ I was wearin' the cross of my calling ♪
♪ On wheels of fire I
come rollin' down here ♪
♪ Come on up for the rising ♪
♪ Come on up, lay your hands in mine ♪
♪ Come on up for the rising tonight ♪
♪ Li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li ♪
♪ Li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, ♪
♪ Li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li ♪
♪ There's spirits above and behind me ♪
♪ Faces gone black, eyes burning bright ♪
♪ May their precious blood bind me ♪
♪ Lord, as I stand
before your fiery light ♪
♪ Li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li ♪
♪ Li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, ♪
(crowd cheers)
♪ I see you Mary in the garden ♪
♪ In the garden of a thousand sighs ♪
♪ There's holy pictures of our children ♪
♪ Dancin' in a sky filled with light ♪
♪ May I feel your arms around me ♪
♪ May I feel your blood mix with mine ♪
♪ A dream of life comes to me ♪
♪ Like a catfish dancin'
on the end of my line ♪
♪ Sky of blackness and sorrow ♪
♪ Dream of life ♪
♪ Sky of love, sky of tears ♪
♪ Sky of glory and sadness ♪
♪ Dream of life ♪
♪ Sky of mercy, sky of fear ♪
♪ Sky of memory and shadow ♪
♪ Dream of life ♪
♪ Your burnin' wind
fills my arms tonight ♪
♪ Dream of life ♪
♪ Sky of longing and emptiness ♪
♪ Sky of fullness, sky of blessed light ♪
♪ Come on up for the rising ♪
♪ Come on up, lay your hands in mine ♪
♪ Come on up for the rising tonight ♪
♪ Come on up for the rising ♪
♪ Come on up, lay your hands in mine ♪
♪ Come on up for the rising tonight ♪
♪ Li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li, li ♪
♪ (crowd cheers) ♪